I’m excited to announce that
preorders are now open
for my How Not to Age Cookbook,
which will be out April 22!
The cookbook is filled with
more than 100 recipes
developed in conjunction with
the great Robin Robertson.
Not only is every recipe
health-promoting,
but every ingredient of every
recipe is health-promoting.
Wait!
How do you make things
sweet without sugar,
salty without salt?
Those are some of the
challenges we faced
to come up with
delicious recipes
focusing on some of the
healthiest of healthy foods,
even in those Blue Zone longevity
regions around the world.
Find out more at
nutritionfacts.org/books
and as always,
all proceeds I receive from
the sales of all of my books
are all donated to charity directly,
to make you and the
world a better place.